Oh, I don't know, do you want
me to hold your paintball trophy
- while you open the door?
- Oh.
Trophy-holding's
only for winners.
Ouch.
No, but, seriously,
today was so fun.
What are you up to tomorrow?
You want to grab dinner?
Uh, actually I can't.
I have to go to a thing
with another woman.
And now it's my
turn to say, "Ouch."
I-It's my nonna.
Uh, she's old-school Italian,
so the two of us always
do Sunday dinner together.
Uh, don't get jealous,
but she does always
kiss me good night.
I lived in Italy
for a few years.
Sì, uh...
Okay, someone
only learned the food words.
Well, I couldn't cook. How
else was I supposed to eat?
Tell me more about
this Sunday dinner.
Nonna goes all out... I mean,
Sunday sauce, handmade pasta.
She spends the entire
day in the kitchen.
How cool. You know,
I love dinner.
And I'd love to meet
your grandmother.
Uh... yeah.
I'm not sure we're there yet.
Oh, really?
I mean, I just thought we were.
Uh, yeah, no, it's ju...
It's just that her place is
really, really small, so...
Well, I'll make Sunday dinner.
Didn't you just
say you can't cook?
Well, I couldn't cook then,
but now... I'm amazing.
Handmade pasta? I'm
a master at that
cranky machine thingy.
Come on, it'll be fun.
Tomorrow night.
Okay... sure. Yeah, uh,
we'll see you tomorrow night
for dinner at Carly's Cucina.
That means kitchen.
Yes, it does.
Spencer, can I host a really
important dinner party
here tomorrow night, so
I can meet Wes's grandma?
I can? Thank you.
Ooh! Meeting the family?
Sounds like you're
getting serious,
like me and Maeve and
our perfect relationship.
Oh, there's my Sleeping Beauty,
freshly risen from
dozing the day away.
Mmm. Well...
I wouldn't need a
nap if my sweet baby
didn't snore all night.
Oh. I could've sworn I
was the one up all night,
thanks to your
ocean noise machine.
- Nothing more soothing than the sounds of seagulls.
- Mm.
- Squawk! Squawk!
- Mmm.
I love those birds.
Maybe more than I love you.
Just kidding.
- Bye.
See?
Aren't we adorable?
That was my nightmare.
Seems like you burned right
through the honeymoon phase,
and now you're on
to the next one.
Which is what?
The "smean" phase...
Where everything's mean,
but with a smile.
Carly, check it out...
The perfect look
for Double Dutch's first music
video with a real budget.
It's kaleidoscope like her
first single "Kaleidoscope."
And it's tattered like her
second single "Tatters."
And it's elegant like
her third single...
- "Ugly."
- Uh
yeah, so ugly.
Wow, the disrespect.
Double Dutch is on the rise,
and she's counting on me to
help her get to the next level.
Like, where would Gaga be
without her meat dress?
Or where would Katy Perry
be without her cupcake bra?
Wait, should I be doing
something with food?
I don't know, I don't
want to think about food.
I invited Wes and his
grandmother over for dinner,
and he said we
weren't there yet.
But you've been on nine dates.
I know. So after that,
I pushed him just a little,
and he said, "Sure."
Ooh.
I know.
Now I have to make
this gourmet feast.
- You don't cook.
- So I can impress his grandma.
Who he didn't want you to meet.
And then maybe he'll
define the relationship
and ask me to be his girlfriend.
You two haven't done that yet?
Oh, I mean, yes!
Great plan. Manifest, queen.
But, look, you don't
have to pretend to cook.
Just be your authentic self.
:
Hello, Harper Designs,
Miss Pennyfeathers speaking.
How may I help you?
: It's Dutch.
: I'll see
if Miss Harper's available.
Aw, Miss Pennyfeathers,
the hardest-working fake
assistant in the biz.
: Mm-hmm. Dutch!
How are you?
I hear you're having
a dinner party,
which is perfect timing because
I just finished the beta version
of the app I'm developing.
Can I give you the
Barracuda Boardroom pitch?
Fine. I'll pretend
to be a wealthy,
overly judgmental investor
that can make or break you.
Freddie Benson is
an app designer
from Seattle, Washington.
He's cool with fish,
cruel with bedtimes,
and he's come here today
to share an app that's going
to revolutionize cooking.
Hey, Barracudas.
Whipping up a big meal is hard.
With all the different recipes
and ingredients and timing,
who can keep it straight?
That's why I created
Bon Appe-timer,
the app that takes the
guesswork out of kitchen work.
Just drag in your recipes
and the app alerts you
every step of the way.
This is exactly what I need.
- Well, I'm in.
- You're right.
Kaleidoscope, tatters,
elegance... it's so passé.
I don't know why my
assistant pulled that.
: Please
don't fire me, Miss Harper.
I need this job
to feed me family.
: All right,
I'll give you one last chance.
Yeah, girl, she been
messing up a lot.
I got to say, Freddie's
app is saving my butt.
I couldn't decide between
rigatoni, ziti, or spaghetti,
so I found a recipe
that uses them all.
It's called Raviolo Maximo.
It's the Turducken of pasta.
Yeah, Turducken, yum.
Wow, the disrespect.
Sorry, I'm distracted.
Dutch has hated the last
five looks I've shown her.
If this one's not a
hit, I'm probably fired.
Do you think she'll like this?
Reminder, I am very fragile.
Yeah, she's gonna love it.
But if she doesn't, are you
just gonna bail on it again?
If I want to keep my job!
I can't just tell Double
Dutch what I think.
But isn't that exactly
what you're hired to do?
Carly
sweet Carly.
You know nothing.
I've been saying that for years.
Oh, that reminds me.
Millicent, I am begging you,
please be nice to me tonight.
You got it, Aunt Carly.
Wes really hit the
jackpot when he met you.
Already bribed her?
Yep. I wanted you to be able
to focus on what matters
the most tonight.
Defining my
relationship with Wes?
No, the real star
of this evening...
My app.
- Ooh, pasta's ready.
- Great news!
Figured out how to stay
in the honeymoon phase.
I found this book How to
Stay in the Honeymoon Phase.
Listen.
"The first thing you
should know is that
"for every relationship,
the honeymoon phase
ends at some point."
This book was written
by a mean liar.
Okay, he's here.
Uh, remember, this dinner
is really important to me,
so everyone be on
their best behavior.
Welcome.
Uh, sorry, I came
straight from work.
Carly, this is my nonna Sylvia.
: It is so
nice to meet you.
Uh, this is my brother
Spencer, that's Freddie
and his daughter Millicent,
and my roommate Harper.
: Hello!
What a nice-looking
bunch you are.
And, Carly, aren't
you a stunner.
Thank you, Sylvia.
Oh, call me Nonna.
- I'm gonna change real quick.
- I'll take your coat.
- I'll finish setting the table.
- I'll get drinks.
Well, I guess it's just me
and you, Nonna.
Oh, good, because I have
something to tell you.
I don't like you.
This is a disaster.
Wes's nonna hates me.
If she doesn't like me, there's
not gonna be a relationship.
- Aah!
Time to layer the three
pastas inside the raviolo!
Uh, Spencer, Harper,
go entertain Nonna.
You got it.
Don't leave it to the
amateurs when you've got
a pro in the house.
Grannies can't resist
this.
Carly, I will not let you down.
Wow. What did you
bribe her with?
Bon Appe-timer stock options.
She said it would round
out her portfolio.
Hi, Nonna Sylvia. I'm Millicent.
Want to see me do a cartwheel?
I'd love to.
Why don't you do a few
out in the hallway?
But then you won't
be able to see me.
Exactly.
Yeah, you're screwed.
Oh!
Here's my handsome Wesley!
Carly? You're the angel
I prayed would
land on this earth
for my grandson.
- She's really into praying.
To who?
- Oh. Uh...
Time to put the
raviolo in the oven.
Wait, this doesn't make sense.
How am I supposed to
put the raviolo in
when the garlic bread's already
baking at another temperature?
- Hang on a second.
- Okay.
- Uh, here.
Oh.
:
Hello, Harper Designs.
May I place you on a brief hold?
At least Spencer's still there.
- : Spencer!
- Got to go.
Great news, nothing
wrong with the app.
It was user error.
How do people on TV make
dinner parties look so easy?
That Barefoot Contessa
is a lying she-devil.
Do you need some help, chef?
Oh, no need.
Everything's running smoothly.
I'm very impressive.
Wow.
Look at all these people that
no one told me were coming over,
my little social butterfly.
It's almost like you heard
them, knew they were here,
and chose not to say hi,
my precious hermit crab.
What a fun, little play
you must be rehearsing for.
Since nobody fights at
important dinner parties.
: Love you!
Big problem.
There's a problem?
- Here, I can help you.
- Oh, no. No, you can't.
'Cause there's no problem.
You're not gonna leave, are you?
Of course not. Dutch
is coming here.
- What? When?
Now-ish? Look,
I promise it'll be real quick.
She insisted on seeing her
video outfit in person.
Carly, if I don't nail this
assignment, I could lose my job.
Okay, just keep
it inconspicuous.
Of course. Nonna won't
even know that she's here.
I assume everyone
knows who I am. No.
I don't need your names.
I will call all
of you Josephine,
after my sister,
whoms I don't like.
Please-please tell me this is
not the outfit you wanted me
- to see.
- Uh...
This dumb thing?
No! No.
I don't think it's
dumb. I think it...
It's smoking!
It's on fire!
Dinner is moments away.
You screwed me, Benson.
You had the garlic bread
too close to the broiler.
That's not on me.
Ugh! Where is my outfit?
The shoot is tomorrow.
Um, I'm gonna be
totally honest with you.
My assistant Miss Pennyfeathers
is on her way with it.
Okay, well, how far is she?
'Cause I was already
hungry, and now the smell
of charred garlic
bread has me ravenous.
Oh, well, do you want to...?
Stay for dinner?
Oh, I would love to!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
That just came out of me.
Carly
do you mind if Dutch
stays for dinner?
Oh, cool.
An unexpected guest,
who also happens to be a
high-maintenance indie darling,
at the most important
dinner of my life.
We're having fun!
Um, I'm not a huge
fan of tomatoes,
so I'm not gonna do the pasta.
Um, but it's okay. Don't worry.
I will just take whatever
the chef's alternate meal is.
Thank you, Josephine.
You screwed me,
too, Bettencourt.
Carly, if
you don't let me help,
I'll never come over again.
Okay, fine.
Um, could you just make
sure that there...?
Serving spoons? Already got 'em.
What are you wearing?
Something downright adorable
to make that old broad like me.
Ah.
Well, hello, Mrs. Wes's Grandma.
I was hoping that we could
sit next to each other
during dinner, and you could
tell me about the good old days.
Oh, I would love to.
There was this glorious time
a few minutes ago
when you weren't here.
It's official.
I've lost my mojo.
"Meal complete. You are done."
I am? That was so fast!
- Moment of truth.
Uh... is it supposed to be
pulsating?
The pulsating's how
you know it's done.
I did it.
I can't believe I did it.
Everyone, let's eat!
Oh!
This is a beautiful table!
And look at the pulsation
on that raviolo!
Thank you, Nonna.
Uh, Maeve, my sweet love, would
you like to sit next to me?
No.
I'm really happy we did this.
I knew we were ready.
I just love seeing all your
faces around the table.
It's so great that
She's choking!
Nonna's choking! Here, get up!
Okay.
Let go of me!
What are you doing?
You were choking!
- Are you okay?
- I wasn't choking.
I ate a bite of raw sausage
and was trying to spit it out,
when this one jumped on me!
I thought you were dying!
I'm sorry, did you
say "raw sausage"?
I have a broken rib.
And I have a broken app.
I am so, so sorry.
I need to lie down.
Uh, you can use my place.
Here, I'll take you.
Aah! Don't touch me!
Yeah, Carly. I'll take her.
: So
do you think it's
safe to eat the salad?
Well, this seals it.
I don't think Wes wants
to be in a relationship
with an elder abuser.
Come on, I'm sure
his grandma's fine.
That's why we have so many ribs.
Oh, I could go for some ribs!
I'm just gonna say what
everyone's thinking.
- Outback.
- Chili's.
Okay, I can't just sit here
feeling sorry for myself.
I'm gonna go apologize
to Wes and Sylvia.
Aw! Who's this little guy?
Her name is Kevin.
And she lives in my purse.
And now
she lives in my lap.
Can I talk to you
really quick over...?
Oh, yeah.
You want to order a pizza?
Anything but pineapple.
Unless you like pineapple,
in which case, mahalo.
I'm starting to think
that your assistant
isn't coming with my outfit.
No, she's coming.
Uh, maybe her
quintuplets got sick.
Or she had to take her
baby to the airport.
Look, if you and I
can't work together
like a well-oiled machine,
I'm gonna have to
hire someone else.
Well-oiled machine?
Wes's coveralls. Wait, hold
that thought. I need to work.
- If-if that's okay with you.
- Yes, go!
I'll fire Miss Pennyfeathers
when she gets here.
Nonna Sylvia?
I'll let you sleep.
I'm so sorry that I hurt you.
And... I lied about
knowing how to cook.
I just wanted to impress Wes.
And you, 'cause you
mean so much to him.
And I like him a lot.
Like, a lot a lot.
Sorry, maybe that's
too many lots.
I like him a sane amount.
I just really hope that
maybe you can forgive me.
And...
Oh, no.
Why is your hand
so cold and clammy?
Nonna? Nonna?
Oh, my God.
This can't be happening.
Okay, I-I can do this.
I saw a CPR video online once.
- Clear!
- Get off of me!
- Oh, my God!
Wes!
She tried to kill me again!
No! No, no, no. I was
trying to save you.
Carly, what are you doing?
I-I'm sorry. I
thought she was dead!
- Well, I'm not!
- A-And I'm glad!
I am so glad you're not dead.
Again.
Come on, Harper.
Let's see it.
May I present...
Greased Lightning.
Aah! No, you may not.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I don't love Grease.
First of all,
you need to put some respect
on Olivia Newton-John's name.
- Oh.
- And second of all,
this is the look.
It says you are the
well-oiled machine.
You're in the driver's seat.
- Skrr, skrr.
- Oh. Oh.
- You leave the competition in the dust.
- Ooh.
Honey, you're miles ahead.
Oh! Okay, enough car puns.
I'm into it.
You are? Um, I mean,
of course you are.
It's so Dutch.
Oh!
I love Dutch.
Where has this Harper
been this whole time?
Terrified of losing her job.
Aw. Well
maybe she can be
slightly less terrified.
She loves that for her.
There you are.
This is where I go when
I need to get some air.
Did we move too fast?
Only according to
everyone we know.
I mean, I built you the
Titanic for our first date.
Do you think that
was a bad omen?
I love you, Maeve, but I
think we need some space.
Hmm. Of course we do.
Because my immature
sweetie has never been
in a real relationship before.
Because my honey
bunny has trust issues
from lying to her friends
and family for four years.
I guess we both got
some growing up to do.
Maybe one day we can grow
back towards each other.
Hmm. I'd like that.
I'm not gonna live
on a boat. No.
You okay, Spence?
Nonna's waiting in the car.
So... I should head out.
I'd say today was fun, but...
I know it wasn't.
And I'd say see you later,
but I know you're
never gonna call me.
You were right.
We weren't ready.
Carly
no one is ready
to meet my nonna.
You probably didn't
notice 'cause I told her
to be on her best behavior,
but she can be a serious pill.
I don't think so.
Most pills have
healing properties.
You know
my last girlfriend would
have let her choke.
Are you saying that
I'm your girlfriend?
Does this answer your question?
- Not really. I mean, am I your girlfriend?
- How about this?
Damn it, Nonna, stop
salting my game.
Mmm.
Can't go wrong with
spaghetti tacos.
Mm-hmm.
This was so worth the wait.
You know what, I get it now.
Kevin, I know we just
met a few minutes ago,
but would you be interested
in moving in with me?
I'll build you a boat.
Kevin's more of an
independent woman,
but if you want,
you can watch her tomorrow
during my video shoot.
I would love that.
This little lady's
gonna help me through
the toughest day of my life.
You know, studies have shown
that petting a dog
is very therapeutic.
Unless your allergic.
Then you'll just get hives.
And too bad there's no way
to connect people who need
pet sitters with
people who need therapy animals.
Like an Airbnb but for pets.
I'll call the app...
Kevin.
Yeah, I need her back now.